Look beyond what you see
Earthquake Bird is a drama, mystery, romance film directed by Wash Westmoreland.
Tokyo, Japan, 1989.
Lucy Fly, a foreigner who works as a translator, begins a passionate
relationship with Teiji, a mysterious man obsessed with photography.
Lucy Fly, played by Alicia Vikander.
Lily Bridges, played by Riley Keough.
Teiji Matsuda, played by Naoki Kobayashi.
Natsuko, played by Kiki Sukezane.
Mrs. Yamamoto, played by Yoshiko Sakuma.
Det. Oguchi, played by Ken Yamamura.
Earthquake Bird is a 2019 psychological thriller film written and directed by Wash
Westmoreland based on the 2001 novel of the same name by Susanna Jones.
It stars Alicia Vikander, Riley Keough, Naoki Kobayashi and Jack Huston.
It had its world premiere at the BFI London Film Festival on October 10, 2019.
It was released on November 1, 2019, before digital
streaming on November 15, 2019, by Netflix.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, love triangle,
photographer, interracial relationship, tokyo, japan.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.